-
Speaker 1: I went to school in 1997.
- So
Speaker 2: you've been paying this student debt for 30 years?
-
Speaker 1: Yes, and I've been in and out of default. It's been a nightmare. I was under garnishment.
Speaker 3: You're making minimum wage instead of garnish your wages.
-
Speaker 4: They did garnish my wages. I have the pay stubs here. - Well,
I
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): borrowed almost $40,000 to go to school back in the '90s.
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): the interest just compounds. It's a worry in the back of your mind constantly. And when you're trying to plan for the future, or even when you want to spend some money doing something fun, if we want to take our grandkids to an amusement park or something, I kind of feel like,
you know,
we're
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): not going to be able to do something special like this when these garnishments restart. And it breaks my heart. And I don't know how they're going to get to college and that... I'm
Speaker 7: sorry. It just really breaks my heart.